# Curriculum Vitae

## **SUMMARY**

I had studied programming while in college, and decided to further develop my programming skills, especially in web programming. I have over 1 years of experience as an Frontend Developer and passion for responsive website design and mobile-first design

#### **INFORMATION**

Full Name : Akhsan Bayu Riantama

Place, Date of Birth : Jayapura, 3 February 1999

Gender : Male

Address : Jl. Kopeng KM 5, Tegalrejo, Magelang

Email : akhsanby@gmail.com

Phone Number : +62895401224170

#### **EDUCATION**

## STMIK Bina Patria, Kota Magelang - S.Kom

October 2017 – Desember 2021

Graduate as Informatics Engineering student with GPA 3.49 by produce a final assignment about step prediction with AI

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

Digireg Indonesia - Frontend Developer
March 2022 – February 2023
<ul> <li>□ Work in IT Development as Frontend Developer to develop WebGIS interface</li> <li>□ Collaborate with Backend Developers in creating APIs to create responses that match the needs of Frontend Developer</li> </ul>
Revise and create website-based company supporting tools according to company requests
Mitra Payment Indonesia - Technical Support
July 2023 - December 2023
Helping clients find solutions to payment gateway problems

☐ Educate new clients on how to use the company's payment gateway platform

☐ Recording bugs on the payment gateway platform to be forwarded to the development team
☐ Assisted with several changes to the frontend appearance of the platform indirectly through pull requests on GitHub
EXPERTISE AND SKILLS
Programing Language PHP, Javascript
Framework / Library Laravel, Codelgniter, VueJS, ReactJS
<b>Design Tools</b> Inkscape, Figma
TRAINING & COURSE
Course Coding Online in Dicoding Academy 2020 - 2021
<ul> <li>Learn the basics of HTML and CSS as the pillars of a website.</li> <li>Learn the basics of JavaScript, from the fundamentals, syntax and features of ES6, to the concept of automation tests using popular frameworks.</li> <li>Learn a lot &amp; deeply about JavaScript to make website attractive.</li> </ul>
Course Coding Online in Udemy 2023 - Present
Im currently studying Golang : Beginner to Advanced, Laravel : Beginner to Advanced, & NodeJS : Beginner to Advanced with Programmer Zaman Now
Kampus Merdeka with Hacktiv8  August 2021 – February 2022
<ul> <li>☐ I learn basic HTML &amp; Css in Kode.id</li> <li>☐ I learn Javascript ES6: Basic to Advance in Kode.id</li> <li>☐ I lean Styling Component ReactJS in Kode.id</li> <li>☐ I learn how to use ReactJS &amp; React Native with reusable components &amp; write clean code in Kode.id</li> </ul>

# **SOCIAL MEDIA**

**Github -** https://github.com/akhsanby

Portfolio web - https://akhsanby.vercel.app

**Linkedin -** https://www.linkedin.com/in/akhsanby